[
  {
    "actual_location": "auditorium",
    "directions": {
      "left": "road",
      "right": "sliit_islands",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "main_entrance",
      "back": "anohana_canteen"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "anohana_canteen",
    "directions": {
      "left": "road",
      "right": "auditorium",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "main_building"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "main_building",
    "directions": {
      "left": "anohana_canteen",
      "right": "road",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "basement_canteen",
      "front": "sliit_islands",
      "back": "road"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "basement_canteen",
    "directions": {
      "left": "road",
      "right": "anohana_canteen",
      "top": "main_building",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "sliit_islands"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "sliit_islands",
    "directions": {
      "left": "auditorium",
      "right": "reception",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "main_building"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "reception",
    "directions": {
      "left": "sliit_islands",
      "right": "road",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "main_building"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "business_faculty",
    "directions": {
      "left": "n/a",
      "right": "car_park1",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "juice_bar",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "play_ground"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "juice_bar",
    "directions": {
      "left": "road",
      "right": "play_ground",
      "top": "business_faculty",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "car_park1",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "play_ground",
    "directions": {
      "left": "sliit_beach",
      "right": "road",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "sliit_beach",
    "directions": {
      "left": "road",
      "right": "n/a",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "play_ground",
      "back": "car_park1"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "bird_nest",
    "directions": {
      "left": "open_theater",
      "right": "road",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "road"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "open_theater",
    "directions": {
      "left": "road",
      "right": "bird_nest",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "road"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "volleyball_court",
    "directions": {
      "left": "basketball_court",
      "right": "sliit_islands",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "basketball_court",
    "directions": {
      "left": "vehicle_parking",
      "right": "volleyball_court",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "tennis_court",
    "directions": {
      "left": "engineering_faculty",
      "right": "n/a",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "engineering_faculty",
    "directions": {
      "left": "new_building",
      "right": "tennis_court",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "car_park2",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "new_building",
    "directions": {
      "left": "willium_angliss",
      "right": "engineering_faculty",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "new_building_entrance",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "new_building_entrance",
    "directions": {
      "left": "willium_angliss",
      "right": "engineering_faculty",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "new_building"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "willium_angliss",
    "directions": {
      "left": "n/a",
      "right": "new_building",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "swimming_pool"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "green_house",
    "directions": {
      "left": "lake",
      "right": "n/a",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "lake",
    "directions": {
      "left": "road",
      "right": "green_house",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "n/a"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "car_park1",
    "directions": {
      "left": "road",
      "right": "business_faculty",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "sliit_beach",
      "back": "road"
    }
  },
  {
    "actual_location": "guard_room",
    "directions": {
      "left": "n/a",
      "right": "road",
      "top": "n/a",
      "bottom": "n/a",
      "front": "road",
      "back": "main_entrance"
    }
  }
]
